{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Bontine_Cunninghame_Graham",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/London",
    "human_readable": "Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham was born in London.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9713366627693176,
            "question": "Where was Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8657501935958862,
            "question": "What nationality was Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8324212431907654,
            "question": "Was Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham a writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6923573017120361,
            "question": "Where did Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham spend a significant part of his life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6615163683891296,
            "question": "Was Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham involved in politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6521843671798706,
            "question": "What era did Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham live in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6130163669586182,
            "question": "Did Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham travel extensively?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.535987377166748,
            "question": "What type of work is Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49961817264556885,
            "question": "Did Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham have any notable relationships?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45820778608322144,
            "question": "What is one of Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham's most famous works?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham was born in London.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7912_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham have any notable relationships?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7912_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work is Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7912_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham travel extensively?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7912_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7912_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7912_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7912_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7912_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7912_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7912_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7912_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7912_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7912_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7912_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham was born in London\" based on the context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis answer is correct because all the documents mention that Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham was indeed born in London, as stated in document /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7912/re-ranker-msmarco/3.txt: \"Born in London on May 24, 1852...\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided in several documents, which all confirm that Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham was indeed born in London."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n    }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}